<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Adam Melnyk</title>
    <link>https://adammelnyk.ca/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Adam Melnyk</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 26 Oct 2019 12:16:05 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://adammelnyk.ca/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Following</title>
      <link>https://adammelnyk.ca/following/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 Oct 2019 12:16:05 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://adammelnyk.ca/following/</guid>
      <description>Here&amp;rsquo;s a list of other blogs that I&amp;rsquo;ve been following for a while or just think are cool.
 Julia Evans https://jvns.ca/ An Awesome software developer who always seems to be working on something cool.   The Musings of an Optimist https://ebzzry.io/eo/ A great blog on lisp and other things that&amp;rsquo;s also translated into Esperanto including a great explanation of the Y Combinator   Steve Klabnik https://words.steveklabnik.com/ Creator of the Rust book and more, a great blog on rust and many other things.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Uses</title>
      <link>https://adammelnyk.ca/uses/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 Oct 2019 12:16:05 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://adammelnyk.ca/uses/</guid>
      <description>Hardware I use  I use a Desktop running Pop_OS from System76 after a long stint using some flavour of Ubuntu since about 2008. I use a Dell Ultrasharp 34 monitor that never feels large enough. I have two Raspberry Pi&amp;rsquo;s I use to run my own DNS at home. I have a pair of Sony MDR7506&amp;rsquo;s that I&amp;rsquo;ve been using since about 2010. I use a Happy Hacking keyboard.  Software I use  IntelliJ for Java, Vim, VSCode for almost everything else.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://adammelnyk.ca/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://adammelnyk.ca/about/</guid>
      <description>Adam is a Canadian software engineer from Edmonton Alberta, residing in Austin Texas. Adams hobbies include programming, powerlifting, eating copious amounts of greek yogurt, reading old comic books, and looking for the perfect breakfast taco.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
