<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Adam Melnyk</title>
    <link>https://adammelnyk.ca/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Adam Melnyk</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 26 Oct 2019 12:16:05 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://adammelnyk.ca/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Following</title>
      <link>https://adammelnyk.ca/following/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 Oct 2019 12:16:05 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://adammelnyk.ca/following/</guid>
      <description>Here&amp;rsquo;s a list of other blogs that I&amp;rsquo;ve been following for a while or just think are cool.
 Julia Evans https://jvns.ca/  An Awesome software developer who always seems to be working on something cool.  The Musings of an Optimist https://ebzzry.io/eo/  A great blog on lisp and other things that&amp;rsquo;s also translated into Esperanto including a great explanation of the Y Combinator  Steve Klabnik https://words.steveklabnik.com/  Creator the Rust book and more, a great blog on rust and many other things.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Uses</title>
      <link>https://adammelnyk.ca/uses/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 Oct 2019 12:16:05 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://adammelnyk.ca/uses/</guid>
      <description>Hardware I use  I use a Dell XPS 13 Developer Edition running Ubuntu. I use a Dell Ultrasharp 34 monitor. I have two Raspberry Pi&amp;rsquo;s. I have a pair of Sony MDR7506&amp;rsquo;s that I&amp;rsquo;ve been using for about ten years. CODE WASD keyboard.  Software I use  IntelliJ for Java, Vim, VSCode for almost everything else. I use Spotify for music. I use FireFox for most web browsing, sometimes lynx.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://adammelnyk.ca/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://adammelnyk.ca/about/</guid>
      <description>Adam is a Canadian software engineer from Edmonton Alberta, residing in Austin Texas. Adams hobbies include functional programming, powerlifting, eating copious amounts of greek yogurt, and looking for the perfect breakfast taco.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>